A Guide to the Wills from the Treasurer's Office, 1787-1867
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Wills from the Treasurer's Office, 1787-1867
The Library of Virginia
28458
127 leaves, photocopies
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Transferred, 26 November 1974, from the Virginia Treasurer's Office, Richmond, Virginia.
Scope and Content
This collection consists of wills filed in Treasurer's Office Material, "J. R. and K. Company Guaranteed Bonds, Wills, and Certificates of Qualification of Holders." These wills were removed and photocopied because they were not extant elsewhere.
Contents List
- Will, dated 30 January 1800 and proved 10 November 1800, of Richard Adams of Richmond (8 leaves).
- Will, dated 15 October 1819 and proved 25 January 1820, of Mary Blair Andrews of Williamsburg(10 leaves).
- Order of Probate, 27 February 1804, of Robert Andrews of Williamsburg (4 leaves).
- Will, dated 4 June 1799 and proved 1 October 1800, of John Blair of Williamsburg (3 leaves).
- Will, dated 20 July 1773 and proved 23 October 1787, of James Buchanan of Henrico County (4 leaves).
- Will, dated 19 December 1794 and proved 12 March 1798, of Joseph Cabell of Buckingham County (6 leaves).
- Will, dated 1 March 1815 and proved 26 January 1837, of Dabney Carr of Henrico County (6 leaves).
- Will, dated 18 June 1858 and proved 27 November 1867, of George Edwards of King William County (5 leaves).
- Will, dated July 1820 and proved 26 October 1820, of John Graham of Richmond (16 leaves).
- Will, dated 8 August 1818 and proved 28 December 1818, of James Henderson of Williamsburg (Extract, 15 leaves).
- Will, no date and proved 18 April 1807, of William Heth of Richmond (8 leaves).
- Will, dated 13 January 1858 and proved 5 November 1863, of Richardson Lumpkin of King and Queen County (9 leaves).
- Will, dated 17 April 1794 and proved 14 December 1795, of John Nicholas of Buckingham County (5 leaves).
- Will, dated 20 March 1834 and proved 25 May 1835, of Robert Saunders of Williamsburg (5 leaves).
- Will, dated 5 May 1862 and proved 6 October 1862, of Evelina Tabb of Gloucester County (3 leaves).
- Will of General George Washington: To Which Is Annexed, A Schedule Of His Property, Directed To Be Sold (Alexandria: Printed from the Records of the County Court of Fairfax, 1800) (20 leaves).